<production>
  <speaker-map>
    Alex: alice.wav
    Blair: chandra.wav
    Casey: david.wav
  </speaker-map>

  <script preset="narrator1">
    Alex: I keep telling myself this corridor is ordinary, but the walls lean in every time I breathe.
    Blair: Then stop narrating and open the door.
    Alex: If I open it, the thought becomes a fact.
    Blair: If you do not open it, the fear stays in charge.
  </script>

  <script preset="narrator2">
    Casey: The city below them looked arranged, almost edited, every light in its assigned column of rain.
    Alex: You make it sound like the storm filed a report before arriving.
    Casey: It did, and the report said we were already late.
    Alex: Then read me the rest before the rooftop gives up.
  </script>

  <script preset="outdoor1">
    Blair: The trail bends by the river, so if they are ahead of us we should hear them before we see them.
    Casey: I hear water, wind, and your backpack complaining.
    Blair: The backpack is making a legal objection.
    Casey: Good. Let it object quietly while we cross.
  </script>

  <script preset="outdoor2">
    Alex: The market is three blocks away and somehow every vendor is already arguing with the weather.
    Blair: That is how you know it is a real market.
    Alex: If the rain gets louder, we may have to shout prices back at them.
    Blair: Practice on me first. I only overpay under pressure.
  </script>

  <script preset="indoor1">
    Casey: This kitchen always sounds fuller after midnight, like the tile remembers every conversation.
    Alex: That explains why the room keeps repeating your bad ideas.
    Casey: The room has excellent taste.
    Alex: The room also needs tea before I accept its judgment.
  </script>

  <script preset="indoor2">
    Blair: Close the office door and listen to that echo. Even the filing cabinets sound impatient.
    Casey: They have heard this budget meeting four times already.
    Blair: Then let us disappoint them quickly and go home.
    Casey: Fine, but the stapler stays. It is the only one on our side.
  </script>
</production>
